<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boondocking on El Pudu: Living and working from our Airstream</title>
    <link>https://www.elpudu.com/categories/boondocking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boondocking on El Pudu: Living and working from our Airstream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;#169; 2018&lt;br /&gt;by Matt &amp; Tiffany</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.elpudu.com/categories/boondocking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beartooth Pass Shoshone National Forest</title>
      <link>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/beartooth-pass-shoshone-nf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/beartooth-pass-shoshone-nf/</guid>
      <description>Beartooth Getaway This campsite was a high altitude stunner. We were up around 8600 ft or so above sea level in an alpine tundra. The main reason we came all the way up here was that the temperatures below were extremely hot. We&amp;rsquo;re talking above 95F as we were coming up the Beartooth Highway. Finally things cooled off a bit up here, though not by much. We still were having 85F daytime temps even at this altitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pole Mountain Medicine Bow NF</title>
      <link>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/pole-mountain-medicine-bow-nf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/pole-mountain-medicine-bow-nf/</guid>
      <description>Vedauwoo Overlook We found this spot on Campendium here: https://www.campendium.com/pole-mountain-area
Coming out Monday morning, we saw that quite a few of the spots were occupied. I hopped on the bike and went for a little ride to scout camps and was able to find one within easy reach of the Pudu.
The camp is at the top of the hill on the side of a meadow with a cool rock outcropping and lots of nice sites around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiawatha NF Rapid River</title>
      <link>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/hiawatha-nf-rapid-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/hiawatha-nf-rapid-river/</guid>
      <description>Burning Field This camp is in Hiawatha National Forest outside of Rapid River, MI. It&amp;rsquo;s right off of the main road and we camped only a short distance in on the forest service road. This lead to a bit of traffic, but really only like 5 people total. It made for an easy spot on our way from Denver to NH.
The spot we were at had very little signal (like 2 bars of 4g) that we were able to improve to about 20/10mbit service with the booster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mt Shavano Blm</title>
      <link>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/mt-shavano-blm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.elpudu.com/campsite/mt-shavano-blm/</guid>
      <description>Mt. Shavano BLM Overview This was a very pretty BLM area outside of Salida. It&amp;rsquo;s super close to both Hecla and Stonebridge and only about 10-15 minutes to Walmart. This was our first boondocking adventure and so we wanted to be close to town as well as close to rafting.
Good We stayed at the end of a cul-de-sac overlooking the mountains towards Gunnison. We had a ton of privacy and beautiful views and we were able to burn before Memorial Day Weekend; after which, there was a fire ban.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>